New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Files 6202
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Meeting Files, 1/25/95-5/22/95. (Box 5)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Congressional Breakfast, Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    March 28
  - Adv. Cnl. Omni Hotel Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    April 29
  - Cooperative Ed Class Alb BOCES, Bldg. A, Health Occup. Suite, Albany-Shaker Road, Albany, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    April 3
  - Literacy Meeting w/Denis Allee, Lois Wilson LOB 913, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Public Hearing on S to W Transition, Hamilton Room, LOB Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    April 4
  - Gr. Capital Region Teacher Center, Sand Creek mid. Scho., Sand Creek Rd room 106, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    April 5
  - Labor Members of the NSSB AFL-CIO, 8th Floor, Ex. Room, AFL-CIO Bldg., Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    April 6
  - Labor Legacy Network 100 S Swan Street Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Breakfast Meeting, Ft. Orange Club, Tap Rm, w/ NYSUT, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    April 10
  - US Department of Labor Office of Policy and Research Employment and Training Administration National Skill Standards Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    April 6-7
  - Nat'l Assoc. of Manufacturers, 1331 Penn. Ave, NW Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    April 12
  - Rochester Central Labor Council 6 pm School to Work Meeting 7 pm Central Labor Council, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    April 13
  - Meeting with commissioner Sobol, his office, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    April 18
  - Meeting w/ Ralph & Connie Varcasia, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    April 20
  - NYS Labor Religion Coal. Conference Albany, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    April 24, 25
  - SABA Greater Rochester-finger Lakes, The Inn on the Lake, Canandaigua, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    April 26
  - AFT Executive Council Opryland Hotel, Nashville TN, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    May 1-3
  - Briefing on Legis. Issues Hay Adams Hotel J. Hay room, Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    May 1
  - United Way Symposium Desmond, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    May 8-9
  - UWNYS Meeting on UW Role in Federal Block Grants, Desmond, Albany, NY Room - Ft. Orange, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    May 8, 2pm
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Mtg. Doubletree Islander Hotel, Newport, RI, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    May 10-12
  - SED, Room 307 Re: School-to-Work Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    May 12, 1:30 pm
  - Mid-Hudson Business/Industry/Education Expo. Holiday Inn Fishkill, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    May 12
  - Hamilton-Fulton-Montgomery BOCES/Workforce Prep, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    May 15 8:30am
  - IRRA Meeting, Omni Hotel Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    May 16 12:30pm
  - Meeting with Speaker Sheldon, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    May 17 9:30 am
  - Meeting in New York City Office w/ Segal Company Re: Pension, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    May 18 1 pm
  - JFF National Advisory Gr Boston. MA, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    May 19 10a-3p
  - NSSB Vice Chairman's Mtg. Steuben Shop, 717 56th Street & 5th, 2nd Floor New York, NY, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    May 22 10am
- Meeting Files, 5/23/95-9/9/95. (Box 6)
  - Worker's Memorial Day Rally West Capitol Park, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    April 28
  - Assembly Workers' comp Task Force Meeting, 3rd Floor Speaker's Conference Room, Capital building, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    May 23
  - Workers' Comp Symposium Desmond Americana, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    May 24-25
  - Cornell Board of Trustees Mtg. Rm. HF Johnson Museum of Art, Cornell University, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    May 27 10 am, 1 of 2
  - Cornell Board of Trustees, Trustee Mtg. Rm., HF Johnson Museum of Art, Cornell University, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    May 27
  - Goals 2000 Panel, Regents Room, SED Bldg., Albany, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    May 31
  - School to Work Advisory Comm., Business Cnl, Corporate Woods office, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 8th Annual WNY Awards Dinner, Radisson Hotel Buffalo, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    June 1
  - CIVITAS @ Prague, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    June 2-6
  - AFL-CIO Regional Conference Sheraton Boston Hotel 39 Dalton Street, Boston, MA, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    June 2-3
  - NYS AFL-CIO Lobbyists Meeting, Albany, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    June 5
  - Hearing on the Future of Manufacturing in NYS Hearing Room C, 2nd Fl., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Albany-Schoharie-Schenec. Cities BOCES Graduation Colonie Central HS, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    June 6
  - NYS School to Work Health Field Pilot Panel, Ramada Inn, Western Avenue, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    June 8
  - NYS AFL-CIO Industrial Division Conference Omni, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    June 18-20
  - United Way of NYS 6/14 Committee Mtgs 6/15 Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    June 14-15
  - TV Show Interview New York City, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    June 21
  - NYSUT Board of Directors, Desmond, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    June 26-27
  - NYSUT Board of Directors, Desmond, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    June 26-27 Pt. 2
  - National Skills Standards Bd. IBEW Headquarters, 1125 Fifteenth Street, NW Washington D.C., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    June 26, 8am
  - Center for Youth Appren. Intl Advisory Board of Governors, Southern Maine Technical College Campus (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Charles Cnty. Public Sch Sys Principal's Prof. Develop. Workshop Harbourtown Golf Resort Conf Center, Maryland, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    June 28, 9am
  - ACTWU & ILGWU Merger Conv. Fontainebleau Hotel, Miami, Florida, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    June 28-30
  - Farewell Reception for Comm. Thomas School, terrace Gallery 4th Floor, NYS Museum Albany, New York, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    June 30
  - first World Congress Of Education. International, Harare, Zimbabwe, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    July 19-23
  - Cornell Dinner, P. TenEyck Home Tygot Road, Altamont, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    July 25
  - Harrington for Troy City Council Italian Comm. Ctr. Troy, New York, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - JFF National Leadership Forum on School to Work Transition Boston, MA, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    July 27-29
  - AFT Executive Council Mtg Sheraton Washington Washington D.C., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    July 27
  - National Skill Standards Board Meeting Carlton Hotel, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    July 28
  - AFT Quest, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    July 27-30
  - Porter Scholars Program Mtg. Embassy Room, Ward man Towers Sheraton Washington Hotel, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    July 29
  - TV Show, NYC, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Aug 15
  - National Design Group, University of Minnesota, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Aug 21-22
  - WNYRO Summer Leadership Conference, Peek N Peak Resort & Conference Center Clymer, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Aug 23025
  - NYS AFL-CIO Community Service Conference, Hotel Syracuse, Syracuse, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Aug 27-30
  - AFL-CIO Dept. of Community Service, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Cornell University ILR Groundbreaking Recept. & Ceremony, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Aug 31
  - 4th annual NYSUT Golf Scramble Outing, Eagle Crest Golf Club Ballston Lake, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Sept 1
  - Skill Standards Day Columbus, OH, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Sept 6
  - NSSB Executive Committee, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Sept 7
  - Fiscal Policy Institute @ 46 Cornell Road, Latham (NYS Nurses Association), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    Sept 8
  - NYSUT Board of Directors holiday Inn Turf, 205 Wolf Road, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    Sept 8-9
- Meeting Files, 9/9/95-16/6/95. (Box 7)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Sept 9
  - Ed Gray Celebration @ DC 37 125 Barclay Street, NYC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Sept 10, 2 pm
  - Workers' Comp Managed Care Pilot, Labor Management Comm. Meeting, 100 S Swan Street Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Sept 11, 11am
  - SEFA, DOT Building #5, Rm. 112, First Floor Hearing room Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Sept 13, 12:30pm
  - Nat'l Center for Workforce Prep., @ Center, 7100 Conn. Avenue, Chevy Chase, MD, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Sept 15, 11am
  - WNY PAC Town Meeting Buffalo CLC, Hearthstone Manor, Buffalo, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Sept 16, 9am
  - IRRA Meeting, Albany Omni, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Sept 19 6:30pm
  - NYSCOVE Dinner, Kirker's Steak & Seafood House, Rte. 9 Latham, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Sept 21, 6pm
  - ILR Advisory Council, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Sept 22, 2pm
  - School-to-Work Advisory Cnl. @ The Business Council, Corporate Woods, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Sept 22, 10:30am
  - Meeting w/DOL Comm. Sweeney Building 12, Room 500 Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Sept 25, 11am
  - NSSB, DOL 2 pm (9/20) Bellevue Hotel 8 am (9/21) Room - Bellevue, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Sept 20-21
  - National comm. For cooperative Education, Princeton Club of NY, 15 W 43rd Street, NYC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Sept 26 9a-2p
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Mtg. Governor Calvert house Annapolis, MD, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Sept 27-28
  - Actor's Work Program Training Center, 165 W 46st 16th Floor, NYC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Oct 2, 1pm
  - Staff Meeting, Sheraton NY Hotel & Towers, 52nd Street at 7th Avenue, NYC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Oct 4, 10:30 am
  - NYS AFL-CIO DHP Graduation Women's Self-Employment, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Oct 6 10:30am
  - Army War College, NYS AFL-CIO 48 E 21st Street, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Oct 10, 2pm
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Washington Court Hotel 525 New Jersey Avenue, NW Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Superintendents Work Conf Adv. Board, Teachers College Manhattan, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Oct 13, 11am
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY Room - Statler Hotel, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Oct 12-14
  - WNY Regional Education Conf. The University Inn, Amherst, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Oct 18, 4pm
  - S. Zahuark Labor History Class, Hudson Valley CC Brahan Bldg., Room 204 Troy, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Oct 16, 6 pm
  - Staff Dev. Day, LI School-to-Career Partnership, NY Inst. Of Technology, Central Islip, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Panel Discussion 1:30-3:30pm, Reception 4:30-6:30 pm Royal Ball, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Oct 20, 4:30pm
  - AFL-CIO Convention Sheraton NY Hotel & Tower New York, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Oct 23-26
  - RI Fed of Teachers & Health Prof. Quest Conf., conv. Ctr. Rhode island, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Oct 28, 10:45am
  - Gr. Glens Falls CLC Annual "Merit of Award" Banquet Roaring Brook, Lake Geo, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Oct 28, 6p
  - NYS Labor Legacy Project 100 S. Swan Street Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Oct 30 3:30p
  - State education Dept. Review Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Oct 30, 10:30am
  - Workers' Comp Labor Management Committee Meeting, The NYS Business Council, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Nov 1 11am
  - School-to-Work Before the Board of regents, Education Building, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Nov 2, 10 am
  - NYATEP/NYSDOL Fall Employment Conference, The Omni Albany Hotel, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Nov 2-3
  - 1995 NYATEP/NYSDOL Fall Employment Conference The Omni Albany Hotel (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - National Skills Standards Board, Open Meeting, Portland, OR, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Nov 4, 1pm
  - Northwest Regional Educ. Laboratory, work Now & In the Future Conf., Portland, OR, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Nov 6-7
  - United Way of NYS @ NYSUT Headquarters, Albany, New York, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Nov 8-9
  - Schuyler Inn, 575 Broadway Menands, NY Paul Speak, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Nov 8-9, 1:30pm
  - NYS AFL-CIO Senate Legisl. Action Committee Conf Desmond, Albany, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    Nov 14-15
  - NSSB Executive Committee Corning, 717 Fifth Ave., 3rd Floor, New York, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Nov 14, 10 am
  - Cornell @ The University Club, NYC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    Nov 15, 10 am
  - Rollout the Framework! Polish community Center Washington Avenue Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    Nov 15, 7pm
  - Jamestown Public Schools, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    Nov 17
  - NSSB, Galvin Center for continuing Education, Schaumberg, IL, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    Nov 20-21
  - Educational Politics 608 Humanities Building Room SUNY Albany, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    Nov 28, 6:30 pm
  - Albany School-to-Work Partnership, Kiernan Plaza Broadway and Columbia Streets Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    Nov 28, 5:30 pm
  - Workers' comp Labor-Management Committee Advisory Group 48 E 21st Street, NYC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    Nov 29, 10 am
  - SEFA Statewide Cabinet Meet. @ DOT, Room 112, Albany, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    Nov 30, 2:30pm
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Sheraton NY Hotel, NYC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Annual Labor Recognition Dinner Sheraton NY Hotel & Towers NYC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    Dec 2
  - National Commission for Cooperative Education New York City, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Labor Legacy Meeting 100 S Swan Street Albany, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    Dec 6, 3:30 pm
- Meeting Files, 12/8/95-2/15/96. (Box 8)
  - AFT Voc Ed Comm Meeting Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - AFT Voc Ed Comm Meeting Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Dec 8 2 of 3
  - AFT Voc Ed Comm Meeting Washington D.C., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Dec 8 3 of 3
  - Cornell Academic Leadership Series Meeting, R. Purcell comm. Center, Cornell U., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Dec 11
  - Workers' Comp Managed Care Pilot Program, LMC 100 S Swan Street Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Dec 11, 11am
  - NSSB Executive Committee, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Dec 12, 9 am
  - National Coalition for Advance Manufacturing, Marriot Crystal Gateway Hotel Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Dec 13, 2pm
  - O*NET Occup. Info Sys. @ American chemical society 1155 Sixteenth Street, NW Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Dec 3, 8:30 am
  - National Design Group for Two Year Inst. Of High. Ed of Minn & St Paul Hotel, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Dec 14-16
  - HRDI National Conference Orlando, FL, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Dec 17-19
  - The commissioner's Review of the NYS Ed Dept., Rockefeller Inst. 411 State Street Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Dec 20, 10:30 am
  - Comm. Review of the NY SED Reception, Rockefeller Inst. Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Jan 4
  - NYS SED Staff Meeting Convention Center, Empire State Plaza, Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Jan 4, 10am
  - AFT Northeast Region Mtg. Providence, RI, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Jan 5-6
  - National Skill Standards Board Meeting Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Jan 11, 1 of 2
  - National Skill Standards Board Meeting Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Jan 11 2 of 2
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Condado Plaza Hotel Puerto Rico, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Jan 12-16
  - NYS School-to-work Adv. Cnl. Albany City School's Abrookin Vocational - Technical Ctr. 99 Kent Street, Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Jan 18, 10:30am
  - AFT Regional conferences Orlando, FL, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Jan 18-20
  - NYSUT Ad Hoc Task Force NYSUT Headquarters, 159 Wolf Rd., Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Jan 22, 10 am
  - AdHoc Task Force on Career Pathways NYSUT Headquarters, Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Jan 22, 10am
  - Kentucky's School-to-work Labor conference, Holiday Inn Capital Plaza, Frankfurt, Kentucky, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - GM Super Steel Rally, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Jan 24 12pm
  - Jewish Labor committee Awards Dinner, Sheraton NY Hotel & Towers, New York City, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Workers' comp Managed Care Pilot Program, Labor/Manage. Committee Meeting, 100 S Swan, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Jan 20, 11am
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees Meeting, NYC, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Jan 25-27, 1 of 2
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees Meeting, NYC, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Jan 25-27 2 of 2
  - Fiscal Policy Institute 1996 Budget Breakfast, Garden Room, Empire State Plaza Albany, NY (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Jan 30, 8:30 am
  - NSSB Research Comm. Mtg. 700 11th Street N. W. Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Omni Albany Hotel, 10 Eyck Pl, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    February 2, 6:30pm
  - NASCOVE, San Diego, CA, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Labor Lobbyists & COPE Resource Comm. Mtg. 100 S Swan Street, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Feb 5, 1:30pm
  - Meeting w/ Monika Aring 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Feb 6, 2 pm
  - WNY-NYSUT, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Feb 7
  - The School to Work Academy Sheraton University Inn Syracuse, NY, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    Feb 14-15
- Meeting Files, 2/15/96-5/22/96. (Box 9)
  - New Designs for the Two-Year Institution, Sheraton Biscayne bay, 425 Brickell Point, Miami, FL, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Feb 15-17 1 of 3
  - New Designs for the Two Year Institution, Sheraton Biscayne Bay 425 Brickell point, Miami, FL, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Feb 15-17 2 of 3
  - New Designs for the Two Year Institution, Sheraton Biscayne Bay 425 Brickell point, Miami, FL, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Feb 15-17 3 of 3
  - NYSUT WNY ED 1-4 Room Radisson, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Feb 23
  - AFT Executive Council Sheraton Bal Harbour Hotel Bal Harbour, FL, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Feb 13-15 1 of 2
  - AFT Executive Council Sheraton Bal Harbour Hotel Bal Harbour, FL, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Feb 13-15 2 of 2
  - NSSB Washington D.C., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Feb 21
  - Ulster County School-to-work Conference, Hillside Manor Restaurant, Kingston, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Feb 24, 9am
  - Labor Legacy Network Mtg. 100 S Swan Street, Albany, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Feb 26, 3:30pm
  - NYS AFL-CIO (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - NYS School-to-Work Adv. Cnl, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Feb 26
  - Staff Meeting, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Press Conf. Capitol, LCA Room Albany, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    feb 26
  - Council 82, AFSCME PAC Workshops 3:30-5:30pm Omni Hotel, Albany, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Feb 27
  - NSSB Roundtable w/ Stakeholders Chicago, IL, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Meeting with Tom Murphy at UFT Building, Legis. Dept. New York, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Feb 29
  - NYSUT RA New York City, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Feb 29-Mar 3 1 of 2
  - NYSUT RA New York City, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Feb 29- Mar 3 2 of 2
  - Labor Lobbyists & COPE Res. Committee, 100 S Swan St., Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    March 4, 1:30 pm
  - Workers' Comp Labor-Management Committee Meeting, Business Council, Washington Ave., Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Mar 5, 11am
  - Workers' compensation Managed Care Pilot Program, Labor Management Committee, BS, Cnl, 152 Washington Ave, Albany, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Management Planning Visit to SED, Room 1072 in ERA Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Mar 5 8:15am
  - NYSUT WNY PAC Legislative Cocktail Reception, Salvatore Italian Gardens, 6461 Transit Road, Depew, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Mar 8, 4:30pm
  - Press Conference on Reform of the Workers' comp Law Gramercy Park Hotel, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Nikon School Rm - UN Plaza Hyatt, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Mar 10
  - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement NY Centr Chapter, Luncheon Speaker convention Center, Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Mar 11, 12pm
  - NSSB, Madison Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    March 18-19
  - SED re: STW Grant Room 315, Washington Ave., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    March 21, 11am
  - Central Labor Council Mtg., four Points Hotel, Syracuse, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Mar 22, 2pm
  - NYS AFL-CIO Industrial Union Division, Four Points Hotel Syracuse, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Mar 22-24
  - AFL-CIO General Board Mtg. Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Mar 25-26
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    March 28-29
  - Career Development & Occupational Studies (CDOS) Framework Teleconference, HVC, TROY, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    April 2
  - Annual Apprenticeship Trg. Conference, NYS SOL, The Desmond, Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    April 3, 9:30am
  - 1996 Regional School-to-Work Conference, Corning, NY (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - NYS Labor-Religion Coalition The Schuyler Inn, Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    April 15
  - NSSB Kansas City, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    April 9
  - NSSB Executive Committee @ Corning, NYC, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    April 17, 10am
  - VATEA Business/Labor/Educ. Day Holiday Inn, Amsterdam NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    April 19, 9am
  - Niagara County UT Annual Legis. Cocktail Party, 515 S Transit Road, Best Western Lockport Inn, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    April 19, 4 pm
  - NSSB Research Committee @ NCEE, Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    April 24, 10 am
  - Workplace Learning: The Strategic Advantage Hyatt Regency Milwaukee, WI, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    April 29-30
  - Teamsters Charity Awards Dinner Desmond Hotel, Colonie, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    May 4
  - Assoc. of vocational Adminis. Of NYS, The Desmond Hotel Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    May 6, 6:30 pm
  - Ireland, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    May 8-12
  - NYC CLC Annual Labor Event The Waldorf Astoria the Grand Ballroom Rm-Sheraton, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    March 16, 6 pm
  - IAM 97th Annual convention @ Omni hotel, Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    May 20, 10 am
  - New York State AFL-CIO Legislative Conference, Empire State Plaza, Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    May 22, 10 am
  - AFT Executive council Stouffer Renaissance Mayflower Hotel, 1127 CT Avenue, \NW, Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    May 22
- Meeting Files, 5/22/96-4/26/98. (Box 10)
  - AFT Executive Council, Stouffer Renaissance Mayflower Hotel 1127 CT Ave NW Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    May 22 2 of 2
  - AFL-CIO Northeast council Radisson Hotel Niagara Falls, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    May 28-31
  - New American High Schools Conference, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    May 22-24
  - Cornell University board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY Room Statler, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Labor Legacy Network 100 S Swan Street, Albany, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    June 4, 3:30 pm
  - Bs. Council of NYS Luncheon Museum's Terrace Gallery School report Card Forum, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    June 4, 11:30 am, 1 pm
  - National Comm for Cooperative Education, Drexel University Phil, PA, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    June 4, 12pm
  - STW Advisory Council Retreat Sagamore Resort. Lk. George, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    June 5&6
  - fiscal policy Inst. Rally, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 9th Annual WNY Awards Dinner Radisson Hotel, Buffalo, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    June 6 6pm
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Area Youth Development Program Annual conference, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    June 7
  - Workers' Comp Meeting NYS AFL-CIO Offices Albany, NY, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    June 10, 7pm
  - NSSB Executive Committee Members Meeting, Corning, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    June 11, 10am
  - FBI & Assem. Fran Pordum, "Improving State Business Climates while Making Development incentives More Accountable", 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    June 14, 9:30am
  - Binghamton Press & Sun Bulletin Editorial Board Meeting w/ Frank Rossner, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    June 19, 2pm
  - National comm. For Cooperative Education, Princeton Club of New York, NY, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 17)